camsonline.com 2018-07-17

# Computer Age Management Services

###  CAMS Privacy Policy

CAMS Privacy Policy confirms to our commitment to privacy and demonstrates the ways we ensure that data privacy is protected. CAMS Privacy Policy applies to the Sensitive Personal Data or Information (SPDI) of all our Customers / Investors and Clients that is in our possession and control. We request Investors / Clients / Customers to kindly read this Policy on Privacy carefully.

CAMS either directly or through third party service providers collects, receives, possesses, stores, deals or handles information received from investors, client, customers whether existing or prospective. The information can be personal and sensitive in nature as given below in the indicative list :

  * Bank Account details, change of bank account details or registration of multiple bank accounts etc. through forms;
  * Payment instrument details at the time of submitting forms at the time of investment or as proof for carrying out change of bank account or any other details of debit card obtained (if any);
  * Generation and storing password (PIN) in encrypted form based on the request from the investor under the online mode of investments;
  * Biometric information obtained, if any;
  * Demat account details like beneficiary account no. etc.;
  * Annual Income and savings profile; and
  * Other information as may be considered as sensitive and personal.

The aforesaid information is being collected by CAMS or third party service providers to service you better and also to be in complaint with Know Your Client (KYC) norms under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act 2001, (PMLA), the rules issued thereunder, and guidelines and circular on Anti-Money Laundering issued by SEBI and allied SEBI related Regulations, as amended till date.

**This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:**

  * How is Personal Information Collected 
  * How is Personal Information used
  * How Personal Information is Shared 
  * How access to Customer Information is limited to employees
  * Information Security 
  * Data Retention & Erasure
  * Incident Management

###  Personal Information Collected

**We gather information that you provide to us when you:**

  * Personal Information Collected Online through our website and mobile applications
  * Purchase products or services through AMCs / Brokers or directly approaching CAMS ISCs to avail the services.
  * Make an inquiry, provide feedback, submit correspondence, or make a complaint over the phone, by email, on our website or by post
  * Register for, and update an online account with us 
  * Enter into a contract with us 
  * CAMS may use cookies to collect information

###  Personal information is Used

CAMS use information to Comply with laws, guidelines and regulations that govern the financial services in the country. To detect, prevent illegal activities, fight spam, and protect the rights and property of clients. CAMS may use the information shared by Clients regarding the products and services to enhance the service related improvements. Reports are generated to protect and defend the rights, interests of Clients products and services. 

We also monitor Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser supplied information and site session information may be recorded as part of the normal operations and for security monitoring purposes.

Some of our products and services collect information about system and product data. We use this information to manage and administer our products and services, to issue updates and new versions, testing and monitoring services that we provide, enhancing our products and services, and improving and targeting our communications with you. 

###  Personal information is shared

CAMS shall reveal only such information to external authorities to comply with applicable laws including cyber laws, based on relevance to comply with applicable laws and to third party service providers such as distributors, banks, sub-brokers, call centers, custodians, depositories to ensure smooth functioning of the activities.-

###  Access to customer information is limited to employees and Third Parties

CAMS limits access to personally identifiable information to those employees with a business reason for knowing such information about investors. We regularly educates our employees on their responsibility to protect the confidentiality of investors’ information, and hold them accountable if they violate this privacy policy. We ensure to enter into suitable terms with third party service providers to protect client confidentiality and follow non-disclosure agreement (NDA).

###  Information Security

To protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, CAMS is a ISO 27001 – ISMS certified company and also use security measures and controls that comply with applicable laws and regulations. These measures may include device safeguards and secured files and buildings as well as oversight of their third party service providers to ensure information remains confidential and secure.

###  Data Retention & Erasure

We ensure that we meet the ‘data minimization’ and ‘storage limitation’ principles and that personal information is stored, archived and destroyed compliantly and ethically. We have dedicated erasure procedures in place to meet the new ‘Right to Erasure’ obligation and are aware of when this and other data subject’s rights apply; along with any exemptions, response timeframes and notification responsibilities. CAMS may retain the data as may be provided by the client till such time as may be provided under the law and as required to efficiently provide service to the clients. 

###  Incident Management

Our Incident Reporting procedures ensure that we have safeguards and controls in place to identify, assess, investigate and report any personal data breach at the earliest possibility. Our procedures are robust and have been disseminated to all employees, who are aware of the reporting lines and steps to follow.

###  Changes to this Policy 

CAMS reserves the right to change this Policy at any time by revising it. This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. By accessing CAMS website, you acknowledge and fully understand CAMS Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates. 

###  Consent 

By accessing this web site and any of its pages you are agreeing to the Privacy Policy. Clients shall not be covered by this Policy, if they access other websites using links from our website. 

###  Privacy Redressal 

If Clients / Customer / Investors have any concerns relating to their personal and sensitive information they may be addressed to [privacy@camsonline.com.](mailto:privacy@camsonline.com)
